

w sasconcept.ftp.cc

M (+852) 6040 8671

Е

shirau@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

A seasoned digital product designer with 9 years of experience designing products across various sectors including retail, education, gaming, bank and digital advertisement business. Proficient in user-centered design processes, specializing in rapid prototyping, interaction design and final user interface visual design. Looking to excel in both analytical and creative thinking, and shape better user experience design.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Advisory UX Designer iClick Interactive Asia Limited 9.2014 - Present

- Conduct ongoing research of web-based user interface development best practices
- Build and design prototypes of proposed features in company products
- Come up with user-centered design solutions with teams such as project managers and engineers to understand user needs and business requirements

# UI & UX Designer nBition Development Limited 1.2014 - 6.2014

• Work with a junior designer to design user interfaces of mobile phone applications (games & apps) and reponsive websites. Deliverables included research, interaction flow, wireframes, prototype and final visual design

# Multimedia Designer Justsolve Consulting Limited 5.2013 - 12.2013

- Lead designer and work closely with engineers from conceptualization to final visual design
- Directly communicate and organise work milestone with client
- Deliverables included online & offline products: mobile applications user interfaces, flash animation, promotional materials (prints)

### Multimedia Designer Multimedia Global Limited 6.2012 - 5.2013

- Work closely with designers, programmers and project managers on mobile phone applications and digital showcases (Kiosk) interfaces, websites and offline marketing materials
- Various client projects including Hang Seng Bank, Sands Macau, Joint Publishing HK...etc

### Senior Graphic Designer Fingerprint Limited 8.2009 - 6.2012

- Print design and web design for marketing and branding services
- Produced artwork for client in-store decoration.
- Communicate and organize the output process and timetable with clients
- Completing tasks by collaborating with junior colleagues

# **Graphic Designer Suncolor Limited 5.2008 - 7.2009**

- Print design and web design for marketing and branding services.
- Printing composing and directly deal with clients' technical output problems

# **INTERNSHIP**

# Web Designer Big Fish Design Limited 10.2007 - 12.2007

Produce front end design and html of websites

### Student Assistant (Major: Design) HK Polytechnic University 12,2006 - 2,2008

• Create posters, web banners, website layouts, video editing of school faculty promotions

#### **EDUCATION**

# **HD in Multimedia Design & Technology**

Hong Kong Polytechnic University 2006-2008

### Secondary 1 to 7

Munsang College (Hong Kong Island) 1999 - 2006